http://www.autoitconsulting.com/site/about/privacy-policy/

Home » About Us » Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy
AutoIt Consulting (“AutoIt Consulting”, “our”, “we”) is owned and operated by AutoIt Consulting Ltd.IntroductionAutoIt Consulting strongly believes in respecting individuals’ right to privacy. AutoIt Consulting will never use your personal data for any use beyond that stated or the permissions you give us or as required by law. This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy“) aims to give you information on how AutoIt Consulting collects and processes your personal data when you use www.autoitconsulting.com and www.autoitscript.com (“Website“).This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions of Use and our Cookie Policy.The Website is not intended for children (those aged 13 and under) and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.When you register or use the Website you will be asked to “opt in” to our Privacy Policy i.e. to confirm that you agree to our use of any personal data that we may collect from you as a user of the Website as set out in this Privacy Policy. If you do not give your consent, you will not be able to use the Website as we will be unable to provide our services and facilities to you. You can withdraw your consent to our use of your personal data at any time by cancelling your membership (see Your Rights).What information do we collect?What is personal data?Where this Privacy Policy refers to ‘personal data’ it is referring to data about you (or other living people) from which you could be identified – such as your name, your contact details and even your IP address.By law all organisations in the UK are obliged to process your personal data in certain ways and to ensure that you are given an appropriate amount of information about how they use it. You also have various rights to seek information from those organisations about how they are using your data, and to prevent them from processing it unlawfully. For more information about these rights, please see the ‘Your Rights’ section of this Privacy Policy.Data we collect from youAutoIt Consulting may collect, process and use your personal data (including your name, postal address, email address, telephone number, mobile number and technical data including your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this Website (“Technical Data”).We collect this data in a number of ways, including through:Direct interactions. You may give us your identity, and contact details, by filling in forms or by corresponding with us by post, phone, email or otherwise. This includes personal data you provide when you:create an account on our Website;subscribe to our publications;give us some feedback.Automated technologies or interactions. As you interact with our Website, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies, server logs and other similar technologies. We may also receive Technical Data about you if you visit other websites employing our cookies. Please see our cookie policy for further details.Third parties. We may receive personal data about your from various third parties, for example, Technical Data from analytics providers such as Google based outside the EU.How we use your personal dataWe will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you.Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.Generally we do not rely on consent as a legal basis for processing your personal data other than in relation to sending third party direct marketing communications to you via email or text message. You have the right to withdraw consent to marketing at any time by changing your account settings or by contacting us.We have set out below more specifics on how we use such data.Server LogsAutoIt Consulting may collect your IP address to produce a server log – as all web servers do. This information is used solely for monitoring the volume of traffic the site receives and measuring the number of readers. We do not use the information for tracking the activities of specific visitors to the Website.AdvertisingAutoIt Consulting runs advertising from Google / DoubleClick. The respective privacy policies of these ad servers can be found here. DoubleClick has a cookie opt-out facility here.Email and Online FormsAs previously stated, if you choose to subscribe to our forum, or complete any of our online forms, you may be asked to supply personal data. If you choose to do so, that information is recorded and used for broad demographic information, which may be used to target advertising. If permission is granted, this information may be used to target specific users with occasional emails informing you about commercial services provided by AutoIt Consulting; and offers from our partners.AutoIt Consulting will never use your data for anything beyond the reason stated and the permissions you grant us. To alter the emails which you receive from us, including unsubscribing from all email communications, please visit this page. Make sure that you enter exactly the same email address as you used to sign up.Change of purposeWe will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to get an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us.If we need to use your personal data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.Please note that we may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.Disclosure of your personal dataDepending on how and why you provide us with your personal data. We may share it in the following ways:if required to do so by law or if we believe that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of the Website or its visitors.With our service providers. We will use third party service providers to undertake processing operations on our behalf, and this may require us to share your personal data with them. These service providers provide us with a variety of administrative, statistical, and technical services. We will only provide service providers with the minimum amount of personal data they need to fulfil the services we request, and we stipulate that they protect this information and do not use it for any other purpose. We take these relationships seriously and oblige all of our data processors to sign contracts with us that clearly set out their commitment to respecting individual rights, and their commitments to assisting us to help you exercise your rights as a data subject. For example, if you use a credit or debit card to make a payment to us, we will send your details to PayPal, who we employ to do our online payment processing. AutoIt Consulting will not keep your card details, other than the type of card used. However, details may be stored by our payment providers (i.e. PayPal) for the purposes of processing further payments you have instructed us to collect.PublishingWe reserve the right to publish emails and letters sent to AutoIt Consulting. If you ask not to have your identity revealed, that information won’t be published. We never publish a private email address unless specifically asked to do so by you.Links to third party sitesPlease note that where we provide links to third party websites that are not affiliated with AutoIt Consulting such sites are out of our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy, regardless of whether they use our branding or logo on their websites. If you access third party sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you that could be used by them, in accordance with their own privacy policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.How long do we keep your information for?Data retentionWe will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirement.In some circumstances you can ask us to delete your data: see ‘Your Rights’ below for further information.In some circumstances we may anonymise your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.Data storage and securityAutoIt Consulting takes the protection of your information very seriously. We use encryption (SSL) to protect your personal data when appropriate, and all the information provided to AutoIt Consulting is stored securely once we receive it.AutoIt Consulting may store your personal data on secure servers either on our premises or in secure third party data centres.1&1 Internet, whose servers are located in the EEA, hosts our Website.Your RightsAs a data subject you have a number of rights in relation to your personal data. Below, we have described the various rights that you have, as well as how you can exercise them.Right of AccessYou may, at any time, request access to the personal data that we hold which relates to you (you may have heard of this right being described as a “subject access request”).Please note that this right entitles you to receive a copy of the personal data that we hold about you in order to enable you to check that it is correct and to ensure that we are processing that personal data lawfully. It is not a right that allows you to request personal data about other people, or a right to request specific documents from us that do not relate to your personal data.You can exercise this right at any time by writing to us using the contact details set out here and telling us that you are making a subject access request. You do not have to fill in a specific form to make this kind of request.Your Right to Rectification and ErasureYou may, at any time, request that we correct personal data that we hold about you which you believe is incorrect or inaccurate. You may also ask us to erase personal data if you do not believe that we need to continue retaining it (you may have heard of this right described as the “right to be forgotten”).Please note that we may ask you to verify any new data that you provide to us and may take our own steps to check that the new data you have supplied us with is right. Further, we are not always obliged to erase personal data when asked to do so; if for any reason we believe that we have a good legal reason to continue processing personal data that you ask us to erase we will tell you what that reason is at the time we respond to your request.You can exercise this right at any time by writing to us using the contact details set out here and telling us that you are making a request to have your personal data rectified or erased and on what basis you are making that request. If you want us to replace inaccurate data with new data, you should tell us what that new data is. You do not have to fill in a specific form to make this kind of request.Your Right to Restrict ProcessingWhere we process your personal data on the basis of a legitimate interest (see the section of this Privacy Policy which explains why we use your personal data) you are entitled to ask us to stop processing it in that way if you feel that our continuing to do so impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms or if you feel that those legitimate interests are not valid.You may also ask us to stop processing your personal data (a) if you dispute the accuracy of that personal data and want us verify that data’s accuracy; (b) where it has been established that our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it; (c) where we no longer need to process your personal data (and would otherwise dispose of it) but you wish for us to continue storing it in order to enable you to establish, exercise or defend legal claims.Please note that if for any reason we believe that we have a good legal reason to continue processing personal data that you ask us to stop processing, we will tell you what that reason is, either at the time we first respond to your request or after we have had the opportunity to consider and investigate it.You can exercise this right at any time by writing to us using the contact details set out here and telling us that you are making a request to have us stop processing the relevant aspect of your personal data and describing which of the above conditions you believe is relevant to that request. You do not have to fill in a specific form to make this kind of request.Your Right to PortabilityWhere you wish to transfer certain personal data that we hold about you, which is processed by automated means, to a third party you may write to us and ask us to provide it to you in a commonly used machine-readable format.Because of the kind of work that we do and the systems that we use, we do not envisage this right being relevant to the majority of individuals with whom we interact. However, if you wish to transfer your data from us to a third party we will consider such requests.Your Right to stop receiving communicationsFor details on your rights to ask us to stop sending you various kinds of communications, please contact us.Exercising your rightsWhen you write to us making a request to exercise your rights we are entitled to ask you to prove that you are who you say you are. We may ask you to provide copies of relevant ID documents to help us to verify your identity.It will help us to process your request if you clearly state which right you wish to exercise and, where relevant, why it is that you are exercising it. The clearer and more specific you can be the faster and more efficiently we can deal with your request. If you do not provide us with sufficient information then we may delay actioning your request until you have provided us with additional information (and where this is the case we will tell you).Contacting usIf you wish to contact AutoIt Consulting Ltd regarding any aspect of the Privacy Policy you should use the following contact details.Other Articles You May Like
Cookie Policy
Terms of Use
Windows 7 Self Optimizing Boot Process
Windows 7 Aero Theme Not Enabled After Deployment
Automating Office 365 Click-to-Run First Use Without Group Policy
About UsContact UsCompany DetailsPrivacy PolicyCookie PolicyTerms of UseRecent Posts
SCCM Package and Program Return Codes and Reboot Behaviour
SCCM Package Success, Reboot and Retry Return Codes
SCCM Create Task Sequence Media Wizard and Network Ports
Single Instance WinForm App in C# with Mutex and Named Pipes
Script to Detect if Running from SCCM Task Sequence and Avoid False Positives
GImageX v2.2.0 Released for Windows 10
AutoIt Cmdlets for Windows PowerShell
WinPE Version List
Automating Office 365 Click-to-Run First Use Without Group Policy
Get the Current Script Directory in PowerShell, VBScript and BatchSite NavigationForumServicesSoftwareAutoItAutoIt ToolsWindows 10 Telemetry GPO PackOSD BackgroundGImageXLogoff ScreensaverVDI OptimizerSCCM SDKOverviewSCCM SDK FundamentalsBlogAbout UsContact UsCategoriesCategoriesSelect CategoryDeployment  (17)Development  (2)Hosting  (1)Image Engineering  (2)Networking  (1)Performance  (3)Scripting  (3)Site News  (1)
Archives Archives
Select Month August 2018  (3) July 2018  (1) June 2018  (2) July 2015  (2) February 2015  (1) October 2014  (1) August 2014  (1) January 2014  (2) November 2013  (1) February 2013  (1) November 2012  (1) February 2012  (2) January 2012  (2) July 2011  (1) June 2011  (3) May 2011  (3) April 2011  (3)
